JASKIRAT KAUR

jaskiratkr29@gmail.com

647 675 9079

Prampton, ON L6Z 4S9

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Well-published Computer Faculty with 3 years of experience designing and implementing research programs and mentoring students in academic institutions. Excellent oral and written communication skills led to high student feedback ratings of 9. Looking for sales associate job in a retail store to implement sales skills to help customers.

SKILLS

- MS Office applications proficiency
- Planning and Coordination
- Organization and Time management
- Stocking and Replenishing
- Sales
- Product and Service Sales
- Point of Sale Knowledge
- Exceptional Customer
 Service
- Merchandising understanding
- Client Service
- Relationship building
- Sales expertise
- Shipment processing
- Cash Handling
- Machine Operations
- Quality Controls

EDUCATION

Punjabi University
Ropar • 04/2013

Master of Science: Information Technology

WORK HISTORY

Lululemon Canada Inc. - Shipper/Receiver *Mississauga*, ON • 10/2022 -

- Inspect all incoming merchandise and shipping materials.
- Place items in correctly sized crates and containers for shipping to customer destinations.
- Accurately complete all paperwork and continuously use wrist and hand scanners to document changes.
- Inventory incoming and outgoing items.
- Affix labels to incoming merchandise from suppliers to input quantities into system and determine correct location for routing to storage or shipment areas
- Use warehouse equipment such as pump trucks

Novatech Patio Doors- Screens Co-Ordinator *Woodbridge, ON • 01/2022 - 09/2022*

- Visual quality inspection of products
- Ensure database records are kept up to date
- Calculated inventory and update it on the internal port
- Order new parts as and when needed
- Maintaining the records in Microsoft Excel

Punjabi University
Ropar • 04/2012

Post-Degree Certificate:

Computer Science

Punjabi University
Ropar • 04/2011

Bachelor of Science:

Computer Science

- Preparation of metrics reflecting recruitment and screening activities and communicating with appropriate internal stakeholders
- Any other duties as assigned by line manager

Giraffe Foods Inc. - Machine Operator Mississauga , ON • 09/2021 - 11/2021

- Attention to detail, ensuring every bottle/ container fills to the correct amount
- Calculated weight, conversion charts, scaling, basic problem solving
- Conduct basic daily maintenance of machines
- Perform machine changeovers, troubleshooting, work with hand and power tools, set ups and take down of packaging machines
- Operate different machines

Canadian Tire Inc. - Shipper Receiver

Brampton , ON • 07/2021 - 09/2021

- Check warehouse for space when deliveries are coming in
- Counting and inventory of products coming in and out.
- Signing off when products are leaving and arriving.
- Checking for damages
- Inspect finished products to ensure it conforms to customer requirements
- Monitor operation of conveyor systems and clear bottle jams from lines
- Assemble boxes and cartons and may hand-pack materials as required

Hamilten Kent - Machine Operator

Etobicoke , ON • 05/2021 - 07/2021

- Visual quality inspection of products online
- Attention to detail, ensuring every bottle/ container fills to the correct amount
- Calculated weight, conversion charts, scaling, basic problem solving
- Conduct basic daily maintenance of machines

- Perform machine changeovers, troubleshooting, work with hand and power tools, set ups and take down of packaging machines
- Operate different machines

Fourth Dimension Solution - Computer Instructor Delhi, Delhi • 12/2015 - 08/2017

- Attended professional development technology courses to increase knowledge base and learn new information.
- Set up computers and networking systems and delivered step-by-step instructions on basic use.
- Created clear, engaging lessons to draw interest and develop students' ability to program in MS Office.
- Met with students outside of class to answer questions, explain difficult concepts and address individual concerns.